O.K.
we have our gloves on.
And we are going to cover the eyes again.
A little bit more water.
You want to cover the eyes for the protection of the light.
So there we are, stay away, turn the light, bright light.
Grab some tissue.
And you want to use tissue just a little more protection so that you are not irritating the skin as much.
Move the light over.
This is 350 Diopter Scope, so the magnifying glass is really gonna help us get into every single pore.
We are not doing this randomly, this is very clear and very precise about which pores we are cleaning out.
So we'll go ahead and get started.
Everything is moving nicely.
The thing about an acne facial, is you never want to force anything from the skin.
You want it all to come easily because the less irritated that the skin is the better.